<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Writing on Advait Rane</title>
    <link>http://advaitrane.github.io/writing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Writing on Advait Rane</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://advaitrane.github.io/writing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Mosquitoes</title>
      <link>http://advaitrane.github.io/writing/mosquitoes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://advaitrane.github.io/writing/mosquitoes/</guid>
      <description>Mosquitoes&amp;nbsp;¶ I haven’t been bitten by these mosquitoes in a while.
These mosquitoes which buzz noisily near your ear,
And hover ominously above your head,
Which make you break that comfortable position you had assumed,
To scratch your ankle, to rid it of the annoying itch.
These mosquitoes which come out only at night,
Like our deepest secrets,
Which pour out of our crevices,
Into the deceptive safety of the dark,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crush</title>
      <link>http://advaitrane.github.io/writing/crush/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://advaitrane.github.io/writing/crush/</guid>
      <description>Crush&amp;nbsp;¶ This gravity won&amp;rsquo;t leave me be as I fall over and over again I escape only momentarily to be pulled back by my memories and I fall almost willingly under the trance of my ill-conceived notions of serendipity.
The scabs on my knees won&amp;rsquo;t heal because I keep picking them
forcing them to bear the blows that my heart deflects and they open up and the blood that pours out is a brilliant lurid red and I feel the rush of adrenaline and enjoy the ephemeral high until reality comes along and sews my wounds shut and the blood that flows back is cold and blue and seeps into every crevice of my soul and I mourn in the frigidity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gloom</title>
      <link>http://advaitrane.github.io/writing/gloom/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://advaitrane.github.io/writing/gloom/</guid>
      <description>Gloom&amp;nbsp;¶ The gloom is contagious.
Lethargy crawls languorously,
Descending from the lugubrious skies.
Like shapeless blobs of a viscous liquid,
In the absence of gravity,
It rains before the rains.
It preys on the hapless mind,
Drowning the industrious cries,
In the indolent fluid.
The vagabond mind drifts into,
A frustrated apathy towards the present.
It falls into,
The murky puddles of the past.
Throws questions of morality,
And of practicality,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Beach</title>
      <link>http://advaitrane.github.io/writing/thebeach/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://advaitrane.github.io/writing/thebeach/</guid>
      <description>The Beach&amp;nbsp;¶ There&amp;rsquo;s water. There&amp;rsquo;s the massive expanse of waves and ripples, like an all-encompassing Juggernaut, throwing itself around until it crumbles into the sand.
There&amp;rsquo;s the sand. The mixture of crushed rocks, broken bottles, stubbed cigarettes and dichotomies in which you can bury yourself comfortably.
The wind. The wanton wind which runs along your skin, eloping with all your worries, leaving you inebriated with peace.
The reflections. The imitations of reality in broken pieces of glass that could cut your foot as they embellish the sand, trying to capture the truth but only really lying.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
